koptalk.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy & Cookies Policy - KopTalk - Liverpool FC News

**Privacy & Cookies Policy for KopTalk**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email to support @ koptalk.org

KopTalk considers the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by KopTalk and advertisers.

**Log Files  
**  
Like many other Web sites, KopTalk makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons  
**  
KopTalk uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customise our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on KopTalk.  
→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to KopTalk and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Opt out of the Dart Cookie")

**Our Advertising Partners  
**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

Each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policies.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on KopTalk and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

KopTalk has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Third Party Privacy Policies  
**  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. KopTalk’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. If you disable cookies in your browser when visiting KopTalk, you will be unable to use our forums and/or members’ website as a cookie is required to remember you login details.

**Children’s Information  
**  
KopTalk does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children. If a parent or guardian believes that KopTalk has in its forums the personally-identifiable information of a child, please contact us immediately via support @ koptalk.org and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our website.

**Online Privacy Policy Only  
**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. However, KopTalk does not store information other for administration of our services which you have consented to if applicable. We never retain or sell your details.

**In summary:**

  * KopTalk does not sell and will never sell your data i.e. your email address
  * KopTalk only obtains your email address to deliver you our services e.g. access to our forums or members website or inclusion on to an email list e.g. Latest Liverpool FC news updates, that you have opted in to (which you can just as easily opt out of)
  * We only track the locations on our website that you visit to ensure the website is working efficiently and to monitor which sections are popular.
  * Third party vendors, including [Google](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/), use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you that are based on your visit to our site and/or other sites across the Internet
  * You may opt out of using the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)
  * As well as [Google](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/), [Clickio](http://legal.clickio.com/PrivacyPolicy/) and [Amazon](https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&*Version*=1&*entries*=0&nodeId=201149560) may also serve adverts on our website
  * Visitors to our website may visit those advertisers’ websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability) or you can opt out of some third-party vendors’ use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Consent  
**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Update  
**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Monday, December 28th, 2015.

Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
